I had to fly out one time and I don't I
come from a very rural part of the
country which we'll get to here in a
second and the closed airports about
three hours away so I didn't want to
leave my truck at the airport for like
four weeks when I was going to be gone
so what I did I went to a local army
base and they flew me out to the larger
airport is one of those really small
Cessnas like those eight seat planes and
I never flown on one of those before and
I'm looking out the window with this
plane and we're in a line I hear the
woman in front of me say 140 I don't
know what that means but now it's my
turn I walk up there and she said are
you flying to st. Louis yes I am she
said well how much do you weigh why do
you need to know how much I weigh she
said because we've made boarding the
plane according to the passengers weight
so that way the wings stay balanced said
but the first thing I need to do is to
get your bags no the first thing you
need to do is to get her back over here
because there's no way she weighs 140
I'm not trying to embarrass anybody here
but I'm not gonna wind up a story on the
news because this woman doesn't want to
admit she slides through Burger King
every once in a while that's not my
problem
[Laughter]
so now I have to stand over to the side
and like calculate all the lies and
everybody else is telling 140 no you
know the guy walked up these like that
bright weigh 175 yen high school you
weighed 175 so final it's my toes like
mr. thorns right how much do you weigh
apparently 844 pounds
I don't come from a big city like this I
grew up in the trailer park is by now
you've guessed I had somebody asked me
the other day if this is my real voice
like if I had the talent to do voices
this is the one I'm picking
[Laughter]
like man don't worry about it women look
guys with accents no they don't they
like guys with good accents and I see
the difference because I'm working with
a buddy of mine he's a comic he's from
Australia and he's got that big dick
Aussie that English yeah a lot of women
find that really sexy and I have this
and they hear my buddy talks like wow
did you hear that accent I bet that
means he is great with women and they
hear me talks like wow did you hear that
accent I bet that means he can fix my
tractor
[Applause]
which I can but that's not the boy those
two we're not
[Applause]
drop still live in a small town in
Missouri it's called Crocker its
population about nine hundred give or
take and people always ask like man how
can you live in a town that small why I
have advantages you guys don't have I'll
never be the victim of an internet scam
[Music]
I'm getting set up for my fantasy
baseball this year an ad pops off a for
a one-time credit card payment of ninety
nine ninety five we can send you the
links and addresses of eight thousand
hot and available women in your town
tonight no you can't
incorrect
I understand why people make fun of
where I come from I get it I know a guy
that wants to date his cousin I know
that guy and he's asked my advice girls
man what do you think no would be my
assessment of that and he's all upset
like well you know are you serious man
are you serious he goes no it's not what
you're thinking we just have a lot in
common
yeah like uncles
[Laughter]
hey did you know the Drybar comedy has
their own app downloaded right now to
watch save and share clips and you can
watch my whole special